nadine-j.de 2018-08-28

# Nadine Jansen Club

## Data Privacy Policy

Our website may be used without entering personal information. Different rules may apply to certain services on our site, however, and are explained separately below. We collect personal information from you (e.g. name, address, email address, telephone number, etc.) in accordance with the provisions of German data protection statutes. Information is considered personal if it can be associated exclusively to a specific natural person. The legal framework for data protection may be found in the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the Telemedia Act (TMG). The provisions below serve to provide information as to the manner, extent and purpose for collecting, using and processing personal information by the provider.

**[Provider’s name and address]** **[Provider’s telephone number]** **[Provider’s email address]**

Please be aware that data transfer via the internet is subject to security risks and, therefore, complete protection against third-party access to transferred data cannot be ensured.

#### Cookies

Our website makes use of so-called cookies in order to recognize repeat use of our website by the same user/internet connection subscriber. Cookies are small text files that your internet browser downloads and stores on your computer. They are used to improve our website and services. In most cases these are so-called "session cookies" that are deleted once you leave our website.

To an extent, however, these cookies also pass along information used to automatically recognize you. Recognition occurs through an IP address saved to the cookies. The information thereby obtained is used to improve our services and to expedite your access to the website.

You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settings on your browser software accordingly. You should be aware, however, that by doing so you may not be able to make full use of all the functions of our website.

#### GOOGLE WEB Fonts

This site uses so-called web fonts, provided by Google, for the uniform representation of fonts. When you call up a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly. To do this, the browser you use must connect to Google's servers. As a result, Google learns that our website has been accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web Fonts is in the interest of a consistent and attractive presentation of our online services. This constitutes a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f DSGVO. If your browser does not support web fonts, a default font will be used by your computer. For more information about Google Web Fonts, see https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and in Google's privacy policy: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.

#### Server Data

For technical reasons, data such as the following, which your internet browser transmits to us or to our web space provider (so called server log files), is collected: \- type and version of the browser you use \- operating system \- websites that linked you to our site (referrer URL) \- websites that you visit \- date and time of your visit \- your Internet Protocol (IP) address. This anonymous data is stored separately from any personal information you may have provided, thereby making it impossible to connect it to any particular person. The data is used for statistical purposes in order to improve our website and services.

#### Contacting Us

We do not use any Homepage based Contact forms, so no data w´ll be send over the internet. You can send us your Message, with your prefered eMailprogram, to our adresses: [Contact](http://nadine-j.de/contact).

#### Using CCBILL as a payment method

If, while completing your order, you decide to use CCBill as an online payment service, your contact details will be sent to CCBill during the order process. CCBill is a service from CCBill LLC, 2353 W. University Dr., Tempe, Arizona 85281-7223 USA, Phone (480) 449-7750, Fax (480) 449- 8819. CCBill assumes the function of an online payment service and trustee, and offers buyer protection services.

The personal data transmitted to CCBill usually includes your first name, last name, address, telephone number, IP address, e-mail address, or other data required to process your order, such as the quantity of articles ordered, the article number, invoice amount, percentage taxes and invoice details, etc.

This information needs to be transferred to process your order using your chosen payment method, mainly in order to confirm your identity and manage your payment and the customer relationship.

Please note the following however: CCBill may also pass on your personal data to subcontractors or other affiliates, to the extent necessary for fulfilling the contractual obligations arising from your order or for processing personal data in your order.

Depending on the payment type you pre-select in your CCBill account, which may include payment by invoice or direct debit, CCBill will transfer the personal data transferred to CCBill to credit agencies. The information transferred serves to identify you and to verify your creditworthiness with regard to the order you have placed. Please refer to the CCBill Privacy Policy for more information on the credit agencies CCBill transfers data to and which data is collected, processed, stored and passed on by CCBill: <https://www.ccbill.com/cs/policies/PP-consumer-english.html>

#### Using 2000Charge as a payment method

If, while completing your order, you decide to use 2000Charge as an online payment service, your contact details will be sent to 2000Charge during the order process. 2000Charge is a service from 2000Charge LLC, 2353 W. University Dr., Tempe, Arizona 85281-7223 USA, Phone (480) 449-7750, Fax (480) 449- 8819. 2000Charge assumes the function of an online payment service and trustee, and offers buyer protection services.

The personal data transmitted to 2000Charge usually includes your first name, last name, address, telephone number, IP address, e-mail address, or other data required to process your order, such as the quantity of articles ordered, the article number, invoice amount, percentage taxes and invoice details, etc.

This information needs to be transferred to process your order using your chosen payment method, mainly in order to confirm your identity and manage your payment and the customer relationship.

Please note the following however: 2000Charge may also pass on your personal data to subcontractors or other affiliates, to the extent necessary for fulfilling the contractual obligations arising from your order or for processing personal data in your order.

Depending on the payment type you pre-select in your 2000Charge account, which may include payment by invoice or direct debit, 2000Charge will transfer the personal data transferred to 2000Charge to credit agencies. The information transferred serves to identify you and to verify your creditworthiness with regard to the order you have placed. Please refer to the 2000Charge Privacy Policy for more information on the credit agencies 2000Charge transfers data to and which data is collected, processed, stored and passed on by 2000Charge: <https://www.2000charge.com/privacy-policy.html>  

#### Information/Cancellation/Deletion

On the basis of the Federal Data Protection Act, you may contact us at no cost if you have questions relating to the collection, processing or use of your personal information, if you wish to request the correction, blocking or deletion of the same, or if you wish to cancel explicitly granted consent. Please note that you have the right to have incorrect data corrected or to have personal data deleted, where such claim is not barred by any legal obligation to retain this data.
